FROM ME TO YOU: KIMI NI TODOKE
3RD SEASON
CHRISTMAS PARTY
Oh, the Christmas thing?
It's after the end-of-term
ceremony, right?
- You going?
- Totally! What you gonna wear?
I just got a really cute dress.
You and Andy signing up too, Yui?
We're celebrating together,
but totally!
It says to bring a present!
Any ideas?
Huh? What about you, Sadako?
Gonna go?
We're all signing up, right now.
I... I think that I could go.
I'm just so glad that
you're able to join us this year.
- Yay!
- Last year, we all sang a song at karaoke!
Wah!
For some reason, I'm incredibly excited!
Hey! Not so fast!
How did things end up like this?!
What exactly did I just witness?
We get to spend the holidays together
as a couple this year.
But it doesn't count if it's a party!
I mean, we're talking about
a huge group of people, y'know.
I can't take my eyes off her
for over two minutes, I swear.
And then there's Chizu...
And you're okay with that,
Sawako? For real?
Well, for me, as long as I'm spending time
with Kazehaya, I'm happy.
Besides, I thought that if I was also
with you guys and everyone else,
there's no way that
it wouldn't be fun, you know?
Oh, right, you couldn't make it
to the Christmas party last year, huh?
Yeah.
Well, either way,
I'm pretty sure Kazehaya's figured out
what he's dealing with by now.
Hey, man! Why aren't the two of you
spending Christmas together?
I expect this from someone like Joe,
but not you.
- Wahoo! Wahoo! Wahoo! Wahoo!
- No, it's not.
- It's nothing like that, okay?
- Hmm? Really?
So it's for Sadako?
Just drop it!
You're in love! It's your first Christmas
since you two started dating each other.
Y'know you really oughta
spend it together, makin' out and stuff.
- Dude, I can't! Just back off, okay!
- Mmm?
Got it!
So it's for Kazehaya's sake as well.
Mmm?
Uh...
A Christmas party, huh?
With karaoke?
Shame I can't make it, I sing great.
If you ask me, it's a good thing
no one invited you to come.
And you better not show up.
You idiot!
You understand what day
we're talkin' about, right?
- It says Christmas Par--
- I'm a busy adult with lots of big plans.
I ain't got time to hang out with kids,
you dumb brat!
Got me a date with a nurse
at a group dating thing!
Yeah, I'm pretty convinced
that our teacher's an actual child.
- Anyway, you goin', or...
- Huh?
The hell?!
- Ha! Must suck to be so lonely!
- Well, I'm not. At all!
Also, I never said
whether or not I was going!
Huh? You should go
with what's his name over there.
Miura.
Huh?
Kento?!
But why?
Mr. Pin, I'm sorry,
but could you please not joke about that?
It's just that...
I'm pretty serious about her, y'know?
Huh?! You shoulda said so!
What are you guys
reenacting the Battle of Tennozan?
Way to put the pressure on, man!
Okay, but you need to
seriously cut it out.
Ge... get the hell outta my way!
Two big idiots just make one big obstacle!
Where are you goin'? Piss time?
You are the worst!
Didn't mean to poke the bear.
Whatever! Go to hell!
Ugh! Argh!
I can't believe I've sunk so low
that I'm being lumped in
with Mr. Pin right now.
Hey, welcome to the company of men.
GIRLS' BATHROOM
What's that supposed to mean,
"pretty serious"?
That guy.
He's always talking out of his butt.
Ayane, hey!
What are you doing for Christmas?
Got plans?
Let's see. I have nothing scheduled,
and it's not like I have a boyfriend.
I'll just do that class thing
with Sawako and Chizu this year.
- And you? Think you'll--
- Why don't we spend Christmas together?
Just us.
I mean, all by ourselves.
- Oh, there you are! Hi, Kento.
- Where are we doing Christmas this year?
- I think it'd be nice to try a new place.
- Uh, hi, Ayane.
Come on,
you should totally join us for Christmas.
It'll be so fun!
Thanks, but I have to pass.
- Ah?!
- I'm already doing the class party.
Uh... But I...
See ya. I hope you enjoy.
- Aw! Too bad.
- She would've had a good time!
Wonder if she's still mad about that?
After the ceremony,
let's go home and freshen up.
Where were you guys
thinking of meeting up later?
- Hey...
- Huh?
I can't make it this Christmas.
I'm signing up
for the class party this year.
I'm sorry, girls.
- No way!
- We'll be so lonely!
So, the party. You goin'?
I'm gonna go, so...
Okay! Fine!
I'm not gonna bow out now just 'cause
I know you're gonna to be there too.
I...
I'm goin' anyway.
Got it?
Good to know,
but that's not what I asked at all.
Huh? Whaddya mean?!
All right. I get it.
So... will ya go with me?
Oh-- Ch-- Chizu?
Okay, so how did I seem
during all that, Sawa?
Uh... you were freaked out, like...
Like, this much.
Argh! I knew it!
Argh! I can't do this!
I mean it, it's impossible, this is nuts!
My heart's racing!
I... I think I might really be into
this "love-life talk" stuff!
Like, a lot!
Wait, that's a random thing to say
when nothing's happening!
And besides, shouldn't you be worrying
more about your own--
Uh!
Well, it seems like you're doing okay.
- Uh, no.
- Uh?
Hmm, now that I think of it, it does seem
like something's been bothering Kazehaya.
- Huh?
- Uh... was I not supposed to say that?
Eh, well I don't think he told me not to.
Look over there.
See that?
It's like his mind is somewhere else.
Wild, right? Joe's talkin' his ear off,
but he's not hearing a word he's saying.
- Please!
- At least notice him, man!
Joe can pretty much
babble like that forever, huh?
- Just give up, already!
- So he's stressed?
What you thinkin' of gettin'
for the gift exchange?
Uh, I guess something
like this should work? Yeah.
- Uh, what's that giant lump?
- Rock salt!
I knew I was right about things
feeling a little different than before.
He wasn't just being awkward around me!
Dummy, dummy, dummy.
-I'm such a dummyyyyy!
- So you're going with a bath bomb, huh?
Getting Kazehaya something too?
Yeah. I'm making it now.
Course you are.
So this is probably how it's gonna go.
Kazehaya's most likely
planning to go to the class party,
then also do something else
with just the two of you.
Like, the day before or after.
Maybe he is.
Finished!
Well, I hope he likes it.
What is it that's bothering him?
It didn't seem like Chizu
had any idea what it could be either.
I'll ask him.
Or maybe it's better if I don't.
Oh... but...
No. Maybe I should.
I really want to be there for him.
But is there anything I can do... to help?
Kuronuma, ready?
Uh, um, Kazehaya.
Can you come over here for a second?
- Hmm?
- Follow me.
Uh, what's goin' on?
Well, um... it's just...
Let's go some place more private.
Come on! This way!
OFF-LIMITS
Uh... what's up?
I-- I, uh...
You see, I... I wanted to...
What's wrong?
I wanted to talk.
Has something been... bothering you?
No.
I see.
Maybe... I completely misread things.
- Bye.
- Yeah.
That was scary.
I wanted to talk.
I really thought
she was gonna break up with me.
Has something
been bothering you?
This is exactly why
I can't say anything to Yoshida!
Something on my mind?
These would look good on her.
Like what?
Kazehaya. Kazehaya.
Kazehaya!
Hi. It's been a while, huh?
Y-- yes, it has, sir!
Good afternoon to you!
N-- no, wait, it's dark already,
so good evening.
Wh-- what are the odds,
us bumping into each other here like this?
Oh! Out shopping
for a present for a girl, perhaps?
- I-- it's for Kuronuma, of course!
- Of course.
- What did you pick out for her?
- I still haven't decided yet.
Well, don't even think about a scarf.
I've got that all covered.
Speaking of covered,
take a look at this thing!
It's from Sawako. Handmade!
It's pretty lit, huh?
Y-- yes, sir. It's... "lit."
He scared me half to death!
You and Sawako... are officially a couple.
That's true, right?
Yes.
I see.
So what will you two
be doing for Christmas?
Uh, we don't really
have plans, but...
Oh! Right! Course not!
I already heard all about it.
Your class is planning to get together
for a big party on the 24th, right?
See, her mother... I mean, my wife says
that Sawako would probably wanna spend
the holiday with her boyfriend, with you,
and that we shouldn't
get in the way of your plans.
But, you know, I haven't heard a single
peep about anything like that from Sawako.
And whenever I ask her,
she just says, "Don't be silly!"
So, um, in other words, I mean,
you're not planning anything
just the two of you?
- No, sir.
- Huh?
Well, actually... we'll be with everyone.
Uh... I-- I see.
That's wonderful!
Wow! That just makes me so happy to hear!
Don't catch a cold!
Maybe this really is for the best.
- Hey, who's that short old guy?
- Miura!
- What are you doing here?
- Huh?
Obviously shopping
for a present for a girl.
I've looked in all these stores,
but no luck.
Also, I have no clue
what would make her happy.
Hey. Let's get some tea.
Huh?!
Ah, so that guy was actually Sadako's dad.
Wow! That must have been
a total nightmare for you.
What's the deal today?
It's been nothing but pure chaos.
Yeah, if I'm gonna be honest,
I never expected you to actually agree
to come and have tea with me, ya know?
Huh?
I mean... you did wanna talk, right?
Y'see, there's this girl I'm falling for.
She's mine.
- I'm not talking about Sadako!
- So why are you telling me about it, then?
That's awesome, man.
It'd be better if you said it
in front of Sadako though, she'd love it!
- Wha--
- Hold on!
We could totally reenact it for her later.
What do you think?
Argh! Stop and get to the point, would ya?
Oh boy.
How is it that you can figure out
that I have something to say,
but you have no idea
who I'm talking about?
But, man, Sadako must really
mean the world to you, huh?
The world.
But yeah, I actually did
wanna ask you about something.
Ayane.
That's the girl that I like.
It's not like
I've never gotten any pushback
from a girl I liked before or anything.
But it's different.
Or... maybe I've just never tried
to reach for something that felt
so beyond my grasp before.
I reached out, and we finally...
But...
even when I do reach out, she runs away.
She never lets her guard down.
She's bulletproof.
So why does she have
so little self-confidence?
Maybe it's just the mask she hides behind.
What can I do to get my foot in the door?
Getting a present's tough.
I have no idea what she really likes,
so I don't know what to get her.
And that sucks, ya know?
Or is all of this just... crazy?
No. I get it.
I don't know what,
but I can tell that something in her past
must have really hurt her.
Do you know anything
about Ayane's past boyfriends?
No, not really.
One time, she did come to school
with her cheek all swollen.
No! Why?!
Why were you dating
someone like that, Ayane?!
It makes no sense!
Not when I could... give you so much more.
A relationship that's full of good times,
I could give that to her.
I'd be there for her.
And I'd treat her like a queen!
What the hell is wrong
with these men lately?
Including you! It was happening
in front of you, and you did nothing?
I'm sorry!
No.
That's not...
Right now, I'm... the problem.
Yeah.
I am, yeah.
Me.
So how have things been goin'?
- Y'know, with Sadako.
- Mm?
Things do seem a little strained
between the two of you.
Never mind. Forget that I said that.
What I actually meant to ask
was how you managed to get Sadako
to get comfortable enough
to really open up to you.
I mean, do you think it's that
"wholesome" vibe thing you got goin' on?
What do you think of my energy?
Am I wholesome?
Huh?
I'm not... particularly wholesome though.
And do I really have to be?
But, what does that
even mean, "wholesome"?
Because I... I'm nothing like that. At all.
I'm just not the person
everybody thinks I am.
Probably not what Kuronuma thinks either.
- Come on. You really think so?
- She means the world to me. She does, but...
It feels like she has this image of me
that I'm afraid I just can't maintain.
I want to cherish her...
but how far do I go?
And what if I make her think that I don't?
And I'm pretty sure
she doesn't have a clue
that I'm actually like this.
Huh.
Maybe I had the wrong idea about you.
You and Sadako are so... similar.
No one's said that before.
Bye! If you ever need to unload again,
just let me know,
and I'll be there for you.
Was I the one
who started the conversation?
Sadako, who's always
been branded as, well, "Sadako,"
and Kazehaya, who's always
been branded as "wholesome."
I guess he's trying to rebrand himself
as just "Kazehaya" right now.
Even though neither of them
can see it that way.
Welcome home, Dad!
Hi, Sawako! I ran into Kazehaya.
Oh yeah? B-- but where?
Oh! I can't tell you that!
We talked about that other thing though.
He said your whole class
will be together on the 24th,
but you two have no plans
to do anything the day before or after.
Yeah.
So we'll do ours on the 25th!
It works out! Leave that day free for us.
Sure.
Then also do something else
with just the two of you.
He gently took my hand with his
and then let it go.
I had it all wrong.
I was wrong... about everything.
I wasn't the one
who was putting distance between us,
it was Kazehaya this whole time.
So here's the spiel.
Christmas and New Year's
are just around the corner,
but there better not be any fighting
or drinking or smoking, got it?
No matter how you slice it,
you're all still minors.
If you're planning to go on to college,
study as much as you need.
Everyone else? Well, do what you want.
Oh yeah!
You've got that thing today, right?
The Christmas party?
Well, make sure
you have yourselves plenty of fun.
But you won't have nearly as much
as I'm gonna! And dismissed!
- Winter break!
- The party starts at 6, okay?
- Kazehaya! So for the party prep?
- All good.
Andy and I are gonna go buy supplies.
Gotcha! I think I'll tag along
with you, then.
You're gonna head
straight there from here, right?
Yeah.
Uh...
All right.
I'll see ya.
Sure.
Come to think of it, we parted ways
like this last year too, huh?
Back when we were first-years,
we weren't dating yet,
and we weren't able
to spend Christmas together at all.
And, even though
we can spend it together this year...
...why is it that
I'm more anxious now?
Oh, that reminds me.
What did you end up buying
for the gift exchange, Chizu?
I know you couldn't decide.
I, uh,
still haven't found something.
What? It's today!
Trust me, I understand that, okay!
What did you think was the purpose
of our little shopping trip the other day?
For some reason,
I can't seem to make up my mind.
I told you any single-use item would be
totally fine and to just buy whatever!
Yeah, I know that. I know, but... Argh!
Fine! Whatever! Screw it,
I'll get that one dumb thingy!
Go on home! Bye-bye! I'll see you tonight!
I think I might have
sent her over the edge.
Y-- yeah, maybe.
- And I wonder what "thingy" she meant?
- Mmm.
Ayane!
- Have a happy New Year.
- Whoa!
Hold on! Not so fast!
I'm gonna be
at the class get-together tonight.
What are you going to do
about the Kento Girls?
Uh, "Kento Girls"?
What are you talkin' about?
But I do like the sound of it.
- You should be one.
- Yeah, no way.
I feel like
that shot barely missed me.
Anyway, I'll be there.
Later.
- C'mon, Sawako.
- Uh, okay.
I'll see you later, then, master.
So I'll see you there!
- So what's your take on that?
- Huh?
Kento. I've been wondering
if maybe he likes me.
Yes, he absolutely does! But I can't say.
I'm dying to tell you, but I can't!
- Nah. That'd never happen.
- Huh?
He always says what he thinks people
want to hear, but it's meaningless.
They're just words.
And I'm sure there's no way
he meant any of that.
He is a good person.
Yeah. I know that.
Kento is a genuinely good guy.
Maybe that's why.
Every once in a while,
I find myself wondering
if he really meant something he said.
Huh?
But there's no way he likes me.
Why not?
Sawako, hey.
You love Kazehaya, right?
What's it feel like?
Huh?
I'm not sure.
It's like I'm really happy.
But also, always anxious and on edge.
When Kazehaya's around, I can't breathe.
I could be happy, I could be sad,
I could be having fun,
or I could be worried,
but my heart starts to pound,
and my chest feels tight.
It's hard to explain.
And I have no clue how he feels either.
But even my own feelings are too much.
If whatever's eating at him
is about us, what do I do?
If he's having second thoughts,
what do I do?
If he doesn't like me anymore,
I'm sorry. Sorry.
Something's gotten into me.
This is so strange.
I just can't control myself.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah. Me too.
We're going through different things...
but I feel the same.
And because yours is so different...
I'm jealous.
I really am.
I'm jealous of you, Sawako.
Not just you. That goes for Chizu too.
I see the two of you laugh,
and blush, and get those butterflies.
And cry.
You both have these confusing feelings,
but you still keep trying.
And I'm jealous.
I've never told anyone I like them.
Nope. Never.
Until now...
I've just kinda been going with the flow.
I let the other person's emotions
dictate what I do.
Sawako, back when
I was going out with Mogi,
you asked me
when I realized that I liked him.
Remember that?
Uh-huh.
See, the thing is, that thought
had never even crossed my mind before.
He really blindsided me.
It took me by surprise.
Dealing with other girls
always meant competition.
But being with guys was easier.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Probably made things easier for them too.
What they want from me is pretty obvious.
And all I have to do is give that to them.
But that eventually gets old, you know?
Because I don't love them.
After a while, it starts to feel
like every guy'll be the same.
I can't help it.
That's how I feel.
So, when I slip up
and take Kento at his word,
I get hit with all sorts of emotions,
and I have no idea what to do anymore.
What should I do?
And what do I want?
Do I want a boyfriend or to fall in love?
Am I into him?
Am I not into him?
Have I given up?
Or do I still have hope?
Will I eventually be able to fall for him?
Who knows.
Maybe it's impossible.
There's no one that I understand less
or am more frustrated with, than myself.
Urgh! Sorry! Somehow I ended up
going on a self-absorbed rant.
Okay. So, Sawako,
we were talking about Kazehaya.
I'm so sorry.
When I started thinking about
how you really, truly love him,
I suddenly got all jealous.
I'm not worried about you guys.
But still, I'm here.
She always tries so hard
to help others.
You're so wrong.
This girl who's so kind,
who I love so much.
That's not true!
It's not!
I know that for a fact!
She honestly thinks that
no one genuinely cares for her.
Everyone would love you
if they really knew you.
She doesn't see it.
Ayane, who can do anything
she sets her mind to.
But everyone who does know you,
loves you.
How can she not know how amazing she is?
So, you're telling me,
I'm the one you're crying over?
You're sweet.
It's not that. You're the one
who's always been so sweet and kind.
Oh, come on.
That's only because you're kind, Sawako.
I mean, everyone's
a much better person for knowing you.
No, that's not true.
Not at all!
Thank you though.
Actually, I'm not really
the person that you think I am.
But either way, I know you mean that
with your whole heart,
so I do believe you.
My whole life,
the only people I've connected with
are Chizu and then you, Sawako.
If I'm being honest with you,
both of you are my heroes.
That's the first time
I've ever said something like that.
Well, I'll see you in a bit.
I'm sorry, Sawako.
That made me happy.
I love you.
But I can't be fixed.
I'm... the absolute worst.
It fills a void
that no girl ever could!
That's not...
...true.
They both said the same thing.
But... Kento would be the easy way out.
He's a good guy. I just can't.
I can't get through. Not me.
Not with words.
There's just a much bigger barrier...
that Ayane built
'cause she's unable to accept herself.
Sawa! Hey, over here!
This one's our room, right?
Go on in!
Oh, thank y--
Ladies first.
What did you finally buy
for the gift exchange, Chizu?
Well, I, uh...
Huh?
It's nothing special.
Not even worth mentioning really.
Go. Walk in.
Chizu! Sawako! Let's sit over here!
Kazehaya! We're gonna save you
a seat, okay?
All right, then.
Welcome, Class 2-D and plus-ones.
Let's get this Christmas party started.
Whaddya say?
Cheers!
Does everyone over there
already have a plate?
They're comin' around!
I'm collecting
the presents, guys.
Be passing them around soon,
so just put them in here.
Huh?
Oh! Joe spilled his...
Joe!
Uh... I got you some tissues.
And... Hey, could you help him out?
- Yeah, sure.
- I just bought these!
- They were brand-new.
- How'd this even happen? Honestly.
- Don't just sit there! Help me!
- Ow.
- Don't look at me!
So what do you want me to do?
I... don't know!
I feel bad for him. Yikes.
Those two sure are comfortable
with each other, huh?
Yes, thank you.
Could we get more damp cloths?
Okay, thanks.
Sadako!
Hey! Time to put in a song.
It's your turn.
We really wanna hear you
sing a song next, Sadako.
Please sing for us!
We wanna hear you
sing your song, Sadako!
Please sing!
Huh? Why's it so creepy?
- Uh?
- What's going on?
Uh...
- Oh.
- What?
- Is she gonna sing?
- Oh, okay.
I didn't know she could.
I'm not very good, but...
♪ Life is all about ♪
♪ Supporting one another... ♪
- This is the song she picked out?
- That's as un-Christmassy as you can get.
♪ My body creaks as many times ♪
♪ As there are holes in the ground ♪
Whoo! Yeah!
- ♪ I dig one more hole ♪
- Yeah, dig it!
Hey, Kazehaya.
Our presents are supposed to go
in the box, right?
Uh... Oh, yeah.
Okay!
Kazehaya! Hey, come join us
over here for a second.
Sure.
- ♪ I dig a third hole... ♪
- A third!
Hey, man. Organizing all this
must have been rough.
- ♪ I dig a fourth hole ♪
- What's this? A fourth hole!
Am I right?
-♪ Each time I dig a hole, tears flow ♪
- Another hole and more tears!
- ♪ La la la la laaa ♪
- Now put your hands in the air!
Good job, girls. Really amazing!
I wasn't expecting
Chizu's background vocals.
What can I say? It got me hyped.
I'm so grateful
that you came up to help me out.
I'm not... a good singer.
If I was alone,
I might have brought down the whole mood.
I don't know about that.
It seems like that mysterious song
of yours is quite popular.
♪ If you curse someone, dig two holes ♪
Hey! Thanks for all this, Kazehaya.
- Hoo! Busy guy, huh?
- Well, you could help, ya know?
Nah, I think my talents
lie more with drinking.
- Don't spill that one too.
- I won't!
Hmm?
Kazehaya!
Yeah?
Where do you want this?
After I've got all the presents.
Should I just leave it right here?
Oh, I'll show you.
He's in charge, after all.
Busy guy. And he's a hard worker too.
Yeah.
He is.
He really is a good one, isn't he?
Huh? Wha-- what?!
Hold on.
Are the couples m-- multiplying?
But why?!
Well,
because it's Christmas Eve.
You and Kazehaya
are dating each other, right?
How's that work? What do you do?
Like, when the two of you are all alone?
- Uh... uh...
- Do you kiss and stuff-- Ouch!
You need to learn when to shut up!
Can you blame me?
Kazehaya never tells me anything!
At this point, I kinda assumed
he was hiding that they were going out.
Guys usually brag.
You don't get to decide
what's normal or not for other people!
What's the big deal?
I don't have a girlfriend myself,
so I deserve a little bit of intel! Hm!
He isn't talking about us, but...
That's okay, right?
We're still boyfriend
and girlfriend, aren't we?
- Okay! Come on now...
- Hm.
Let's not focus on other people.
Talk to me about your situation.
Are you interested in anyone special?
Like a girl?
Of course, there's a girl.
There's literally always a girl.
There's no one on this planet who wants
a girlfriend more than this guy does!
So, uh, Yano!
You are a strong candidate. Y'know?
Incredible. Where does
this confidence of yours come from?
I'm genuinely curious.
'Cause... I'm me!
Huh?
You can't have her.
I'm sorry.
There is something you can do.
But you need to change
your approach a little.
How come? Why's she off limits?
Try this. First you go up to a girl
that you really like,
and then you ask her
what she honestly thinks about you.
It works out well.
'Cause she's unlikely
to say anything mean to your face.
Then... just tell her
you're in love with her.
Easy-peasy.
Oh! Yes! Good! And then what? Yeah? What?
So that's how it is.
That's your approach with everyone?
Ask them what they think of you first?
To be honest,
with you, I couldn't.
I told myself "no."
Listen up, everyone!
It's time to start the gift exchange!
We're going to play some music,
and when it stops,
whatever present you're holding is yours.
And we'll break it up into five rounds.
Wh-- what's the matter, Chizu?
Are you all right?
Uh-- Oh! Uh, I-- I'm okay.
Chizuru, what did you
end up buying for your gift?
- Argh!
- Argh! Yoshida spilled her drink!
That's not the point!
It's all about
just enjoying the gift you've been given!
Okay. I think I get it now.
Okay, stop!
I've never even seen this before.
- Wha-- A tawashi scrubber brush?
- Hmm?
Whoa! Looks like I got Kazehaya's.
Huh-huh. Wonder what's inside?
Oh--
I'm...
...jealous!
Are you doin' okay, Sawako?
- Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
- Uh?!
There's a beast!
An insatiable beast
dwelling deep inside my heart!
Oh... kay.
Guess I can take that as a "no"?
Okay, it's gift exchange round 2.
Here we go!
Am I gonna get one this time?!
- What are you hoping for?
- Girlfriend!
Music! Start!
How are we feeling?
Should I stop the music soon?
- Oh! It's all up to you, Chizu.
- He-he!
Sweeeet!
Now, hurry up and pass it!
Okay. Got it.
- Here, Ryu.
- Hmm?
- Ryu, pass!
- Hmm.
- Huh!
- Stop!
All right!
Whoo! Him got one!
That's one point for Joe!
I wonder what's inside it,
and more importantly, who's it from?
That wrapping paper's cute.
So it's gotta be from a girl.
Go on, open it up.
- Okay!
- Oooo!
Here goes!
No! You can't!
Mm--
Waaaaaah!
Chi-- Chizu?
Oh, what should we--
I've got this.
Which coat is hers?
- This one?
- Uh, y-- yes.
That was my present!
Ah. There, there.
Hey, Kazehaya. Let me look real quick.
There it is.
Listen up, Joe.
I'll give you this present.
It's from me, so stop crying, okay?
Uh? From you to me?!
What is it?
It's, uh, one of those things.
Yeah.
It's a stone that brings you luck in love.
If you pray to it every day,
then you'll get a girlfriend.
- You'll be......my girlfriend now?!
- Not what I said.
Chizu.
What was in that present?
It's-- it's cold!
Hmm.
- What are you doing?
- Who cares?!
Don't say anything, just take it!
It's yours! Hey!
Why are you
opening it up right now?!
I bought it for you, Ryu!
It was always meant for you!
I was hoping
that you would end up with it.
So...
And before you say anything,
I get it, okay?
I know what you're thinking!
"What if I wasn't the one
who ended up getting it?"
But I was, like, ya know,
"What if he does get it?"
I mean, nobody could really know for sure.
You might get it and you might not,
and that's just how it is.
But you ended up almost getting it.
You were this close!
Although, I do kinda feel bad for Joe.
A little. I guess.
Argh! Are you even listening?
Yeah.
You were taking a chance on me.
Thank you.
Looks good?
Mmm.
The big doofus looks so happy.
- I got something for you too.
- Huh?
Outside of the exchange.
Here. Open it.
Mmm? Mm. Mmm. Mm-mm-mm-mm.
Oh! There's the damn seam. Found it.
Why did you
get me something like this?
Huh?
It doesn't remind you of yourself?
Wha-- Like me, how?!
Well......I don't really know
how to put it into words.
A single pink rose? How is that like me?
It's a... "preserved flower," they said.
A "pre--" It's a what?
I wonder. Is this the way Ryu sees me?
Argh!
Uh, let's go!
Uh?
Not yet.
We haven't been alone like this
for a while.
So let's make it last.
Yoshida and Sanada
are takin' their sweet time.
- Think maybe they're fighting?
- Joe, are you crying?
Tears of joy.
Chizu.
No need to worry. Yoshida ran outside
without grabbing her coat,
so Ryu decided to take it out to her.
This stuff happens all the time.
Yeah, Yoshida's almost always
acting without thinking first.
Ryu's basically her caretaker.
They could just be dating now?
There's no way!
Huh? Is it really that strange?
She meant it for Ryu,
so that's why she panicked.
And it explains
why she couldn't pick something.
I mean, those two
need to just go out already.
I think they're perfect for each other.
I'm curious though, how Chizu feels.
Well, those two are on their own planet.
Maybe something's happening
no one would understand.
Not that I'd have any clue.
Oh, Ayane, your glass is empty.
Do you want something?
Oh no. It's okay. I can get it myself.
I'm so jealous of Sawako and Chizu.
Sawako!
Chizu, those feelings you just poured out,
does Ryu know?
It's because you fought so hard for us.
Have I given up?
Or do I still have hope?
Will I...
eventually be able to fall for him?
Hmm?
Wah! The heck did I step on?
Argh!
Huh? Uh, was it yours, Kento?
I'm sorry.
I stomped on it pretty hard too.
Oh well,
that's not good.
Is it okay?
Uh, maybe?
I'm gonna take a closer look to make sure.
Oh.
- Sadako.
- Oh, Master.
You look kinda worried.
Is everything okay?
I said she'd be fine, didn't I?
Oh! Master!
What is it? What happened?
Or is Kazehaya
gonna be all upset with me again?
I'm always thinking about my own problems.
Even though everybody else has so many.
Despite that, Ayane, she...
She's always, no matter what... so kind.
And I... I always idolized her.
She's so mature, and I could
only see her as this perfect example.
But... I was wrong.
We're the same.
We really are.
For the first time,
I saw Ayane on the exact same level as me.
Oh, it's no use.
I can't find the right words to explain.
- I get it.
- Uh...
Honestly.
And I really
wanna make things better for her.
Those stupid jerks!
Can't believe they strung me along
like that! Nurse, my ass!
What? You found a better
group of guys for the party?
Argh!
You guys are the worst! Huh?!
Oh yeah! The brats are here!
I need to blow off some steam!
I have the uncontrollable desire
to mess with them right now!
- Was that Pin?
- Uh-huh.
- Wait, Mr. Arai?!
- Hmm? What the hell?!
- You crazy, Kuronuma?! You scared me!
- I'm so sorry!
Don't worry about it.
You did nothing wrong,
so there's nothing to apologize for.
S-- sorry, I won't! Huh.
Not going in? How come?
Well, it's just that, you know...
Ha-ha!
Let me guess, your brain's all fried
from overthinking something?
I'll lend an ear.
I bet it's something about Shota again,
am I right?
Right! Then come with me.
It's not!
It's actually about me
since I only think of myself these days.
And what's wrong with that?
How are you supposed to
help anybody else with their problems
if you don't have your own sorted?
Well, you can't.
Then, I think you found your answer, yeah?
Oooooh!
SCALE
That reminds me,
I saw your Career Interest Survey.
Are you sure that's what you want?
Uh, sir?
Listen... if that's what you honestly want
for yourself, then you should do you.
You're not exactly
a selfless person, you know?
So I am selfish!
Come on. That was a compliment.
Just sayin'.
If something's important to you,
you go out and make it happen.
If it's important to me.
The thing is, maybe this whole time,
I've only done what I've wanted.
I've had so many self-improvement plans.
Like "Becoming the Person
I'm Doomed to Be, Part 1."
Or "Smiling Practice, Part 1."
But every single idea or intention...
was something that I wanted.
I put everything into accomplishing
the things important to me.
Even if it didn't work out.
If I keep at it,
then maybe things will change.
One day.
But, then again... there's no guarantee
all that effort will amount to much.
And now, I have so many people
who are dear to me,
that I'm able to worry
about others for the first time.
Not knowing what I can do to help them,
not being able to keep
my own feelings under control,
it's all because
I didn't understand myself,
how many desires I truly had.
Every day, it feels like there's
something new I can't put into words
or even do.
I want to know everything
about the person I love.
I want everything about Kazehaya
to belong to me.
But I can't have that.
And it feels wrong for me to want it.
I don't want to lose him.
But, if I did, I have no idea what I'd do.
- Ah! Well, that's better.
- Huh?
You're thinkin' about your boyfriend
instead of being worried about yourself.
Just the fact that you were able
to switch your emotions like that now
means that none of this was pointless.
I don't follow.
I guess you haven't worked out
what to do about it quite yet.
Okay, that's all for now!
- Let's talk next semester!
- Oh.
But, hey, when there's something
you wanna protect,
it might seem like there are things
you need to avoid saying.
But if you bottle up
all those feelings of yours,
you'll only make yourself frustrated.
Anyway, those feelings don't mean squat
in the grand scheme of things,
so let 'em out!
If you speak up, as stupid as that kid is,
he might get it.
So just do it.
You already know what to say.
Just tell him exactly what you want.
I can't do that...
and I shouldn't.
But despite that... I want to.
I knew it.
It got totally crushed.
Oh, uh, Mogi?
Let's see, it's like...
How do I put it?
If you can do that,
he'll respect it right away.
I know these things
because I'm such an attentive teacher.
But what are you gonna do?
Shota's always been tough.
It's 'cause he's so stubborn!
As for exactly how stubborn he is,
that boy's as stubborn
as a stubborn old man!
Oh... he... is?
Deep down, that kid can't rest
unless he gets exactly what he wants.
He's his father's son.
Oooooh!
And, oh yeah, about Ryu?
That guy has a really good heart
and a great big spirit.
What do you mean?
Are you dumb? That guy's crazy tough.
Don't underestimate him.
Then there's Yoshida.
Diligent, just in her own way.
Yeah.
She never comes to a test
totally unprepared.
She's actually the type that stays up
to cram like crazy the night before.
The problem is that she's not exactly
clever enough for that method to work out.
Her, uh, self-awareness
is also not her strong suit.
Uh, oh, really?
You're Mogi from Class B, am I wrong?
No, that's right, but...
Oh, you're in Class D.
Ah yeah. For sure. I'm Kento.
Oh yeah.
I totally remember who you are now.
Well, see ya.
That reminds me.
Miura too. He also has a pretty big heart.
Yes.
But he kinda makes me
wanna do something just to piss him off.
That's a nasty face.
Well, my work here's done.
What about Ayane though?
Huh... yeah.
She's doing fine.
But well...
she's still a kid.
Later, then.
Hey! Hold on!
You used to go out with Ayane, didn't you?
Oh, uh... yeah.
So what have we here?
Looks like it's about to go down.
W-- with Master?
And... Mogi?
We met during free time on Okinawa.
- You remember that, don't you?
- Uh...
Y'see, I... sorta ran into Ayane there.
And she told me some stuff.
Wait, Yano... she told you?
Check it out.
They have no idea we've been standing here
watching them this whole time.
How spacey can you be?
Uh, well, she didn't say anything.
I was the one who asked her about it.
'Cause she was hurting.
Look, you've got it wrong.
It was...
Yeah, no...
It worked out okay.
What do you mean by that?
Yano is...
actually mature, like a real adult.
I mean, she was cool with it.
I-- I did kind of feel guilty
after that, ya know?
What did you do?
Well, I didn't really "do" anything.
It's just, at the time...
Maybe I was expecting
a lot more from Yano than I should have?
Like what?
Expecting what?
Are you talking about sex or...
Did you do something to Ayane?
No, it wasn't like that.
Nothing happened, I swear. I kissed her.
That's all.
She was so mature about it.
And she forgave me.
So then, you had
all of these... expectations.
But did Ayane know about them?
Uh, hold on! Are you saying
she didn't tell you anything?
What happened?
The thing is, she overheard me
talking to the guys about us.
- I'm fine.
- I really am okay.
They were just curious.
They all wanted to know what it was like
to have a girlfriend, ya know?
- Like a report?
- Yeah, yeah!
But I lucked out.
When Yano walked up to us,
she didn't seem to be bothered.
Not bothered?
Are you kidding me?!
You're an idiot!
Why would you think it's okay
to tell people something so personal?
If I'm being honest,
I don't think any of the guys I dated
were really that into me anyway.
I'll ask you once more,
what did you do to her?
Seriously,
you're acting like
she disappointed you somehow!
But well, since I am the way I am,
I guess that's just a given.
It's mutual, right?
Did you think for even a second
that Ayane is more than that?
And to consider
how that made her feel?!
- Hey! Ayane!
- Huh?
Okay, that's enough.
Idiot. Didn't I tell you kids
not to get in any fights?
Hey, Mogi, you doin' all right?
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
I thought I heard fighting.
Down that way!
Hey. Kid. Now. Get outta here.
But I...
'Cause if you stay,
things'll just get complicated.
So head over there. The stairs.
Are you okay?
Um, excuse me?
We've gotten a number of complaints
about some sort of commotion out here.
Oh, don't worry about that! All good!
It's just this kid's a real klutz.
He slipped and fell flat
on his ass, that's all. Right?
Uh... y-- yeah.
All right, please be more careful, then.
Yano?
Sorry... about Okinawa.
I didn't realize it mattered that much.
I mean, I just figured...
'Cause, ya know... you didn't care that much
about me anyway.
But... it was awful of me, wasn't it?
I'm sorry.
Back when I first
bumped into you at school,
I liked you right away.
I thought, "Wow, this girl sure is great."
"I'd love to go out with her.
That would be so incredible, wouldn't it?"
And the upcoming school trip
gave me the kick I needed.
To work up the nerve.
I always let you take the lead.
And I never got the chance
to show you a good time.
And, yeah, it's true,
I definitely expected
certain things from you.
But I really did think
you were awesome and gorgeous.
Honestly.
Right.
- I can tell you're not lying about that.
- Uh.
You know what?
I really don't feel any hatred
towards you or anything.
Besides, it's not exactly your fault
that what you did hurt me so much.
It's okay.
I'm actually used to that stuff.
You don't need to say more.
- Thank you.
- Uh...
Have someone else
take care of your nose for you.
Hey.
Miura took the emergency stairs.
And that'll be his Christmas present.
Ayane, you...
What are you doing out here
dressed like that?
It's freezing.
- It's fine.
- It's totally not.
I really blew it.
This was your Christmas present.
It's kind of a mess though.
Did you get hurt?
What are you doing?
I love you, Ayane.
I can't take it.
I don't wanna watch
as you walk away from me anymore.
I... I think you're so cute.
And I love you so much.
The way you're awkward. And a big softie!
I love that!
I love you!
If you've never been in love
with anyone before,
then fall in love with me!
Even if it's not all at once.
Just fall in love with me, okay?
I'll cherish you.
I'll treasure you so much, Ayane!
Okay.